http://www.scand.com/privacypolicy/

Skip to content
ServicesWeb App DevelopmentFront-end DevelopmentBack-end DevelopmentPWA DevelopmentSPA DevelopmentDesktop App DevelopmentMicrosoft Add-insMobile App DevelopmentiOS App Development ServicesAndroid App DevelopmentCross-platform App DevelopmentHybrid App DevelopmentCloud Application DevelopmentStaff Augmentation ServicesEmbedded Software DevelopmentUX/UI ServicesDevOps ServicesQA ServicesTechnologies.NETJavaC/C++PHPJavaScriptReact.jsAngularPythonIndustriesE-commerceHealthcareLogisticsSCMBanking & FinanceFinTechBlockchainTelecomEducationIoTAdvertisingMedia & EntertainmentGambling & GamingExpertiseCRMERPBig DataHRMDigital PublishingDigital Rights ManagementCAD Software DevelopmentAugmented and Virtual RealityPortfolioProductsArchived ProductsCase StudiesR&D WorksCompanyAbout UsLocationEngagement ModelsOutstaffing ModelDedicated TeamPeopleCareersBlogNewsContact usEnRuDeEnRuDe
Home / Privacy Policy Privacy Policy
Scand Ltd. is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. The following privacy statement (further ‘Privacy Policy’) is designed to help you understand all the ways we apply to collect and use the information you provide us with and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site, products, and services. Personal data of our customers and visitors are processed and used with special care. Collecting InformationWhile visiting our website or using our products or services you may provide us with your personal data that you consciously disclose. Also, our website uses information collected on an aggregate basis, as you and other visitors browse our website.We may collect, store and use the following kinds of personal data:information you provide to us by filling in forms on our website (e.g. by requesting the information about our products or services);information you provide to us for the purpose of subscribing to our email notifications and/or newsletters;information you provide to us when submitting your CV (including your contact information);information contained in or relating to any communication that you send to us or send through this website (including correspondence with us, communication content and metadata associated with the communication);information that is required to obtain trial or commercial license of our products or otherwise become a registered user of our products or services;any other personal data that you choose to send to us (i.e. the personal data of a candidate to work who you want to refer);information about your visits to and use of this website (including your IP address, geographical location, browser type and version, operating system, referral source, length of visit, page views and website navigation paths). Use of Information CollectedPersonal data collected by Scand with may be used by Scand for a wide range of purposes:to inform you of new products and services we will be providing,communication about past, current or future projects,feedback and/or editorial purposes,marketing and market research,promotion,recruitment,advertising,license generation,payment processing,customer support,statistical analysis,to record your consent to Scand Ltd to obtain and store your personal data.For the above-mentioned purposes, we use only personal data that we receive from you through contact forms on our website. Please notice, that we require your explicit consent to this Privacy Policy when you submit information through any of our contact forms or during the process of requesting or purchasing licenses for our products.Personalizing and identifying information, such as names, postal and email addresses, phone numbers, and other individual information voluntarily provided by visitors to Scand Ltd. may be added to its databases and used for future telephone calls and correspondence.If you choose to correspond with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses.The information collected through third-party analytics tools such as Google Analytics and Yandex Metrics can be used to carry out statistical analysis of customer behavior, for software development, for content improvement or customization. CookiesLike many other commercial websites, Scand website utilizes a standard technology called “cookies” and web server logs to collect information about how our website is used. Data collected through cookies and web server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at our website, and any websites visited just before and just after visiting our own website.You can opt-out of cookies in your browser anytime, however, please note that you may not be able to take full advantage of our website if you disable them. Third Party Analytics SoftwareThis website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses “cookies”, which are text files stored on your computer to enable analysis of website usage by you. The information about your website usage generated by the cookie (including your IP address) will be transferred to a Google server in the U.S. and stored there. Google uses this information to evaluate your use of the website, to prepare reports on website activity and to provide other services associated with website activity and internet usage to website operators. Google may also share this information with third parties, if required by law, or if such third parties process the data on Google’s behalf. The IP-address that your browser conveys within the scope of Google Analytics will not be associated with any other data held by Google. You can alter the configuration of your browser to refuse cookies, however, please note that you may not be able to take full advantage of our website if you disable them. By using this website, you agree to the processing of data about you by Google in the previously described manner and for the above-mentioned purpose.This Website uses Yandex Metrics which is a web tracking tool of Yandex. Yandex Metrics uses so-called cookies. A cookie is a small text file which is stored on your computer and allows an analysis of your use of the website. The information on your use of the Website as generated by the cookie will usually be transferred to a server of Yandex in Russia and stored on such server. Yandex will, as an agent of the person or entity operating this Website, use such information for purposes of analyzing your use of the website in order to create reports on the website activities and in order to render further services related to the use of the website or of the internet to the person or entity operating the Website. Check Yandex’s Terms of Use for more details: https://yandex.com/legal/metrica_termsofuse/ You can prohibit the storage of cookies by way of a respective configuration of your browser software; we inform you, however, that in this case, you may not be able to fully use all functions of this website. Anonymous data collected through this websiteIn addition to the information which we collect as described above, we use technology to collect anonymous information about the use of our website. For example, our web server automatically logs which pages of our website our visitors view, their IP addresses and which web browsers our visitors use. This technology does not identify you personally, it simply enables us to compile statistics about our visitors and their use of our website.Our website contains hyperlinks to other pages on our website. We may use technology to track how often these links are used and which pages on our website our visitors choose to view. Again this technology does not identify you personally – it simply enables us to compile statistics about the use of these hyperlinks. Links to other websitesThis website may contain hyperlinks to websites that are not operated by us. These hyperlinks are provided for your reference and convenience only and do not imply any endorsement of the activities of these third-party websites or any association with their operators. We do not control these websites and are not responsible for their data or privacy practices. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We urge you to review any privacy policy posted on any site you visit before using the site or providing any personal data about yourself. Third-Party Cloud ServicesSome of our products help users to make data exchange of their desktop software with cloud-based services. In such products Scand Ltd does not obtain nor collect any personal or another information of users, except of their personal data that are required to identify them as registered users of our products. Each time we do so we ask the user for an explicit consent to provide us with this information in conformance with this Privacy Policy.To enable the access of our products to the required cloud-based services, the users will explicitly confirm the corresponding Privacy Policies of such services (such as Google, Amazon, Microsoft and etc.). No Information is Disclosed to Third PartiesWe do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personal data. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our own site policies, or protect our or other parties’ rights, property or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising or other purposes. Terms of UsePlease also take time to visit our Terms of Use section that describes the use, disclaimers, and limitation of liability that governs the use of our website. Your ConsentBy using our site, you consent to conform to our privacy policy. Your rightsThe European Union’s General Data Protection Regulation and privacy laws in other countries provide certain rights for data subjects.You have a right to access and rectify the record of your personal data maintained by Scand Ltd. You are allowed to revoke your consent and request that the Scand erase your personal data or cease processing it, subject to certain exceptions. You may also request that Scand Ltd. ceases to use your data for direct marketing purposes. You have a right to file a complaint with the data protection authority if you have concerns about how the Scand processes your personal data. When technically feasible, Scand will at your request provide your personal data to you or transmit it directly to another controller.If access cannot be provided within a reasonable timeframe, Scand will provide you with a date when the information will be provided.You may also request information on: the purpose of data processing, the categories of personal data, what the source of the information was, and how long it will be stored.If you wish to execute any of these rights or have any questions concerning our personal data policy, please contact our Data protection officer at GDPR@scand.com at any time. Retaining personal dataYour personal data is stored by Scand on its servers, and on the servers of the cloud-based database management services Scand utilizes.Personal data that we are processing based on your consent will be kept for an unlimited period of time or until the consent is revoked, unless demanded by applicable legal requirements and presuming that it is necessary for the purpose of processing.Notwithstanding the other provisions of this Section, we will retain information and documents (including electronic documents) containing personal data:to the extent that we are required to do so by law;if the information/documents are relevant to any ongoing or prospective legal proceedings;in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk). Security MeasuresWe have implemented strict security procedures to prevent the unauthorized release of or access to personal information provided by our customers and website visitors. SCAND has been certified according to the ISO/IEC 27001:2013 information security management standard and uses its methods for handling confidential information. For example, all our employees are required to certify in writing that they accept confidential nature of personal information and the importance of keeping it secure.You should be aware, however, that the transmission of information via the Internet and other electronic media creates certain security risks, and that we can give no guarantee of the safety of information transmitted to us by these means. Right to Change Privacy PolicyScand Ltd. reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time without providing any previous notice. Contact DetailsIf any questions arise regarding this Privacy Policy please do not hesitate to contact us making use of the information below.www.scand.comScand Ltd. 8b/1-520 Fabritsiusa Str., 220007 Minsk, Belarus Tel./ Fax: +375 (17) 256-07-76 E-Mail: contact@scand.com
